What's this?
This is dark magic.
Dark magic?
Magic that turns people into demons with black Rukh.
it is a terrible and very powerful magic.
Why is this happening to them?
This is a magic tool used to heal wounds.
Stop making a mess of my dungeon!
If it continues like this, they become demons for good!
You should end this quickly with Baal's power!
You're just a boy!
He refused even after all we had done....
Sinbad?
Wha-What are you doing?
I must save my friend.
What are you talking about, dumb ass?
If they become fully demon, we'll--
Shut up.
They said want to shape the world with me.
You still think this monster is human?
No!
They are not man or monster.
They are my comrades.
I will not let my comrades die!
You're always like this...
You're not afraid ...?
you cannot return to your country and you are searching...
I don't follow my destiny.
and so... I'm going to show that I can overcome my own destiny.
Why do you fight to shape your destiny so much?
How can you change it ?!
2Nami Subs Presents: Magi: Sinbad no Bouken -Valefor Dungeon pt 2
What's going on?
This destructive power....
What a time to break...
Sinbad, use the power of the djinn!
There is no other way!
We either defeat them right now or we'll be killed!
No, there is still another way.
What?
The monster's core is connected to the humans used to make it.
and it seems like it's trying to drain their Magoi.
The core of it is in the chest.
If it can be destroyed with one blow, the three of them could be saved.
Yes
Bararaq-
What?
Hello, everyone.
Without this, it seems you're powerless.
The Falan witch!
You're the one behind this!
It's true, my real body is at Partevia.
In fact, I'm under direct orders from Master Barbarossa.
From my brother?
Captain Dragul ...
Pardon me, you were promoted two ranks again, you are now lieutenant.
I climbed two ranks? What do you mean?
This means you're already considered killed in action, Junior.
That voice...
Brother?
Failed to conquer the dungeon, then ...
... Failed to capture the dungeon conqueror, Sinbad.
For someone of the famed Dragul family, this is unforgivable.
And above all...
... About my wife.
Did you think I would not notice your feelings for Serendine?
You crossed the line.
She is my woman.
Know your place, and die.
You all were sent here as sacrificial pawns.
You have nowhere to return to.
Drakon.
Hina!
You should have immediately killed the demons with this sword.
I told you already.
I am not going to...
... abandon anyone!
Sinbad ...
You always have been, overcome anything with a strong determination.
I think if I had the power of a king, I could be like you.
But now I understand.
Even if I obtained the power of the king, I could not be like you.
I'm just looking for an excuse to avoid mistakes.
That's enough, Sinbad.
I told you already ...
... that's enough!
Hina.
Every time you're around, I end up getting my ass kicked.
You're always underestimating me.
When fighting the rampaging unicorn, you finished it off.
You beat my opponents without even considering me.
Even now ...
My body is broken and  bruised
But ...
... You're an amazing guy.
Yes.
My destiny is to follow someone like him.
Sin, I'll defeat him!
I am the only one who can finish him off!
Then, I'll keep him busy.
With this I can get a direct hit!
They are really annoying.
What?
This boy, he's somehow avoiding all the attacks!
It's as if he can predict the attacks!
In that case...
Sinbad!
Don't worry about me...
But ...
Do not move, we only have one shot at this!
This need of yours to help others will get you killed.
Die!
Drakon.
i was fighting for my country all this time.
I used to think it was honorable, to die in battle for my country.
But I was wrong.
Who I should protect ...
If you die, I will never forgive you!
Barbarossa.
I will not leave her to you!
I will emerge from this dungeon, and...
... Definitely will come to kill you!
You come to your senses!
Do you not see how shameful this is..
... being under control of their magic?!
What is going on?
Sorry for keeping you waiting!
This is the "First Spear" from the Imuchakk tribe!
I'm not the old me.
I am now sure ...
... this will finish it!
God damn it! How dare you kill my monster!
You should join it!
I believe this is mine.
Still breathing, it seems he survived.
You're awake?
Oi.
Sinbad, you saved us.
Are you okay?
Yes, I feel calm, as if an evil spirit had been separated from my body.
Evil spirit??
What?!
Black rukh again...
Boss!
Impossible.
The demon ...
revived?!
I can recreate it using a human corpse
Plus, this child is already almost dead.
These conditions are perfect for the finished core.
What? Did they say "almost dead"?
This time, the core is the child himself.
Meaning to defeat the monster, you have to kill this child.
Well, will you do?
oi, what do you going to do?
Maybe...
He is trying to save him from inside?!
Stop, the human body can not survive!
What is this?
It feels like it's flowing into my mind
It is the memory of this child.
Now we will go to the subconscious.
Baal?
My lord, I beg of you, save this child.
He will not be able to return from the darkness that remains in this condition.
It hurts...
I don't want this...
Mom ... Dad ...
Where are you?
Oi.
Stop your whining, you're getting on my nerves!
I don't wanna be here. I want to go home.
Home? Do you even have a home?
Quit being a fucking crybaby and face the music.
We killed mother and father!
Kill them, Jafar.
Kill!
We were born into the organization.
One day,  we were required to kill them.
So survive, we need to be strong!
We had no other choice!
There is no other choice...
We had to kill them...
we have to stay alive!
So this is the real you.
With this conflict in your heart, you're lying to yourself, and living in misery, huh?
Shut up! What do you know ?!
You're right, I do not know anything.
But ...
If you've got no place to go, I'll give you one.
I will be the way by which you can keep moving.
So do not lie to yourself anymore.
Because in the end ...
... you found your place.
You heard me, didn't you?! I will not let my comrades die!
Therefore, will not forgive you if you're dead.
Huh? He received his own attack himself?
Look!
Black rukh is coming out of his body.!
Not yet ... Do not give up yet, Jafar!
Hey ...are you still alive?
Yes.
You really did it!
I can not believe ...
he could rescue people who fall into darkness.
This boy...
This treasure room ...
is the place where the Djinn Valefor  will establish a contract with the King's Vessel.
Well then, Choose who will become king!
Sinbad, you're up!
Hina.
All the people here recognize you as king.
Establish the contract with the Djinn, Sinbad, our king!
I accept you as the king!
Sixth Dungeon: Valefor
Conquered!
Looks like we're back.
This time everything is in one place, yes.
Very weird...
Only a little time has passed since we entered the dungeon, however....
it feels like ages ago.
Welcome back!
Father.
I ...
Well, let's go back to the village.
The ceremony is about to begin!
I will take leave from here.
Wait, Drakon!
Ultimately, we are rivals.
Although we were allies in the dungeon,
I have no reason to go with you.
Why are you looking at me like that?!
Nothing, no reason.
You're not being sincere.
Anyway, I'm going back to my country
I am aware that it'll be dangerous.
But despite everything in this place...
... There is someone I have to protect.
I understand. Good luck!
Hopefully we do meet again.
Sinbad ...
If I were a man without a country, I would follow you as my king.
No...I'd better not..
Because if he is my master, my life would be full of problems.
Kinzoku...It is an instrument that shines for Warriors...
that have been blessed by the King and the djinn
Drakon is the first to get this power.
However, the story that uses this power is still there in the future.
Yes, let's go home!
Yeah!
You are now a proud Imuchakk warrior,
As evidence of this, I will now give you something special.
Come close, warrior.
Raging Unicorn horn is proof you're a warrior.
This weapon is the symbol of justice.
May your will be as strong as a million warriors.
Warrior, your name is Hinahoho.
The meaning of your new holy name is "clear like the ocean". Be an honorable warrior!
Yes sir!
Here.
Boss.
Cheers.
Father!
I mean, Elder.
I will leave Imuchakk.
I've decided...no, my destiny has decided
To create a nation that unites the world!
I want to be his sword, his hands, his shield. And achieve their dreams.
I want to establish a new world along with Sinbad.
You are now an Imuchakk warrior.
I am proud of you.
Yes.
Grand Chief, Rametoto
Grand Chef, Rametoto
The warrior Hinahoho, thanks you for hearing us today.
Warriors Hinahoho would would like to request the hand of Rurumo..
in marriage, and to travel the world.
Answer the question first, Warrior Hinahoho.
What can you give to my daughter?
Treasure? Power? Throne?
My daughter has received a variety of my training in order to become the strongest warrior.
He already has everything.
What can you give to someone like her?
There is nothing I can give her right away.
Asshole, how dare you say such lowly things before the head of the federation!
I'll rip you to pieces!
I now can not give anything, but ...
... I can share and realize her dream.
The dream of my love!
Through this conversation, Sinbad ...
... Established a monopoly of trade contracts with Imuchakk.
The name Sinbad the Conqueror spread to the world not only as an adventurer, but also as a merchant.
The merchant fleet, which he founded,
became known as the Sindria Trading Company of the Seven Seas!